Alexus Christensen

Personal Assistant

Roseville, CA 95661 (916) 699-0624 Alexusdc6@gmail.com

Customer Service Representative with 6 years of experience of providing excellent customer service, extraordinary communication skills, and organizational management. Seeking to perform a position where I can grow within a company, but also obtain more personal growth while impacting the lives of others.

EXPERIENCE

Yohana, Palo Alto, CA — Senior Personal Assistant

June 2021 - Present

- Communicating with new and current members (currently 17, one which includes the CEO of the company) on day to day tasks including scheduling appointments or classes, purchasing, researching items or information, planning events and travel, etc.
- Making phone calls to pros and businesses to gather accurate information about products and services, pricing, and availability to provide to members
- Testing out new features given by engineering and providing accurate and candid feedback while also offering solutions
- Efficiently organizing and completing daily tasks for multiple families at one time
- Properly training new hires every week with daily tasks and member management

Miosa Bride, Folsom, CA — Bridal Consultant

January 2021 - June 2021

- Respond to new and current client base regarding complaints and service enquiries
- Working alongside retail representatives to boost sales by presenting new ideas to clients, all while making sure we get the products on time
- Continuously organizing the presentable merchandise to drive further sales
- Confirming new and existing daily appointments per phone and email

Tri Counties Bank, Folsom, CA — Teller

August 2020 - January 2021

- Properly answered client's questions and needs while providing assistance where needed
- Continuously ensured that clients were in the best products available and made changes when necessary
- Handled a high limit cash drawer with little to no discrepancies
- Confirmed all paperwork is within proper guidelines and policies

El Dorado Savings Bank, Placerville, CA — New accounts representative / Teller

March 2018 - August 2020

- Process and monitor all money transfers, maintaining a cash drawer and resolving all cash-related discrepancies and other problematic issues
- Collecting client deposits, addressing any customer requests ensuring optimal customer experience
- Assisting in the management of multiple client accounts and completing daily reports
- Opening products for customers that suits their needs to the best of my capability

IN-N-OUT, Placerville, CA — Level five associate

January 2016 - October 2017

- Processed guest orders, handled cash, prepared food and beverages in an accurate and efficient manner
- Successfully handled multiple customers at one time in a fast-paced environment
- Adhered to establish company and departmental procedures, guidelines, and policies at all times

EDUCATION

UC Davis Continuing and Professional Education - Coding

June 2022 - Present

El Dorado High School - High school diploma - Placerville, CA

August 2013 - May 2017